Can you score 10/10 as a true Indian? Only 1% can pass Question 8.
Question 1. What is the capital of India?
The correct answer is Delhi.
Question 2. Which animal is the national animal of India?
The correct answer is Bengal Tiger.
Question 3. Which is the national fruit of India?
The correct answer is Mango.
Question 4. Which state is known as the Spice Garden of India?
The correct answer is Kerala.
Question 5. Who was the first President of India?
The correct answer is Dr. Rajendra Prasad.
Question 6. Which city is known as the Pink City of India?
The correct answer is Jaipur.
Question 7. Who was the first Indian woman to win an Olympic medal?
The correct answer is Karnam Malleswari.
Question 8. In which year was the first Indian passenger train flagged off?
The correct answer is 1853.
Question 9. Which is the largest state in India by area?
The correct answer is Rajasthan.
Question 10. Who is known as the missile woman of India?
The correct answer is Tessy Thomas.
How many did you get right? Comment your score below!