Only 1% get Question 10 right on this Science Quiz!
Question 1. What is the powerhouse of the cell?
The correct answer is Mitochondria.
Question 2. What is the chemical symbol for water?
The correct answer is H2O.
Question 3. Which planet is closest to the Sun?
The correct answer is Mercury.
Question 4. What is the atomic number of Carbon?
The correct answer is 6.
Question 5. What is the speed of light in vacuum?
The correct answer is 299,792 km/s.
Question 6. Which gas is most abundant in Earth's atmosphere?
The correct answer is Nitrogen.
Question 7. What is the rarest naturally occurring element?
The correct answer is Astatine.
Question 8. What is the half-life of Carbon-14?
The correct answer is 5,730 years.
Question 9. Which particle has no electric charge?
The correct answer is Neutron.
Question 10. Who proposed the general theory of relativity?
The correct answer is Albert Einstein.