Only 1% get Question 10 right on this Science Quiz!
Question 1. What is the powerhouse of the cell?
The correct answer is Mitochondria.
Mitochondria convert nutrients into energy (ATP) for cellular activity.
Question 2. What is the chemical symbol for water?
The correct answer is H2O.
H2O represents two hydrogen atoms bonded to one oxygen atom.
Question 3. Which planet is closest to the Sun?
The correct answer is Mercury.
Mercury is the smallest and closest planet, orbiting in just 88 days.
Question 4. What is the atomic number of Carbon?
The correct answer is 6.
Carbon has 6 protons and is the foundational element for organic chemistry.
Question 5. What is the speed of light in vacuum?
The correct answer is 299,792 km/s.
At this speed, light takes just 1.3 seconds to travel to the Moon.
Question 6. Which gas is most abundant in Earth's atmosphere?
The correct answer is Nitrogen.
Nitrogen makes up 78% of our atmosphere, compared to 21% oxygen.
Question 7. What is the rarest naturally occurring element?
The correct answer is Astatine.
Less than 1 gram of Astatine exists in Earth's crust at any time.
Question 8. What is the half-life of Carbon-14?
The correct answer is 5,730 years.
Its half-life makes it perfect for dating organic matter up to 50,000 years old.
Question 9. Which particle has no electric charge?
The correct answer is Neutron.
Neutrons sit in the nucleus alongside protons and have neutral charge.
Question 10. Who proposed the general theory of relativity?
The correct answer is Albert Einstein.
General relativity proved gravity is the warping of space and time.
How many did you get right? Comment your score below!